(Leonard:)Hey, can I talk to you about something?
It's a little awkward.
(Sheldon:)I know what this is about.
(Sheldon:)Given the professional standstill
you're at...
(Sheldon:)...you're wondering
if this is the appropriate time...
(Sheldon:)...to abandon your research
and focus on teaching.
(Howard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)And if I may suggest,
consider changing disciplines.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, to the humanities.
Perhaps, history.
(Sheldon:)One of the advantages
of teaching history...
(Sheldon:)...is that you don't have
to create things.
(Sheldon:)You know, you just have to remember
stuff that happened...
(Sheldon:)...and then parrot it back.
(Sheldon:)You could have fun with that.
(Leonard:)Yeah, that's not it.
(Leonard:)Stuart's kind of interested in Amy.
Well, of course, he is.
She's very interesting.
(Sheldon:)Did you know, when she was 14...
(Sheldon:)...she severed the webbing
between her own toes?
No. Uh...